export const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is my idea of a perfect date night?",
    options: ["Movie at home", "Fancy dinner", "Beach walk", "Game night"],
    answer: "Movie at home",
  },
  {
    question: "What name would we agree on for a first child?",
    options: [
      "Salem",
      "Oluwashindara",
      "Shiloh",
      "Wonder",
    ],
    answer: "Salem",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these do I fear the most?",
    options: ["Heights", "Losing loved ones", "Public speaking", "Darkness"],
    answer: "Losing loved ones",
  },
  {
    question: "If I could travel anywhere with you, where would I choose?",
    options: ["Paris", "Morocco", "Kentucky", "Ireland"],
    answer: "Bali",
  },
  {
    question: "What habit of mine do you think I want to change?",
    options: [
      "Too afraid to try new things",
      "Snubbing people",
      "Snacking too much",
      "Procrastinating",
    ],
    answer: "Procrastinating",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I like to be comforted when I'm upset?",
    options: ["Left alone", "Cuddles", "Talking it out", "Knacks"],
    answer: "Talking it out",
  },
  {
    question: "What is my favorite way to spend a weekend?",
    options: [
      "Sleeping in",
      "Exploring the city",
      "Staying home with you",
      "Cooking together",
    ],
    answer: "Staying home with you",
  },
  {
    question: "What is one fruit I can't live without?",
    options: ["Pineapples", "African cherry", "Mangoes", "Watermelon"],
    answer: "Pineapples",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I usually handle stress?",
    options: ["Sleep it off", "Talk to someone", "Go quiet", "Cry"],
    answer: "Go quiet",
  },
  {
    question: "Whatâ€™s my love language?",
    options: [
      "Quality Time",
      "Words of Affirmation",
      "Gifts",
      "Acts of Service",
    ],
    answer: "Quality Time",
  },
];
